wrestlingfeed.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | wrestlingfeed

April 24, 2011 || {5,553 views} 

We care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following terms to learn more about our privacy policy.

  * We will never sell your personal information, or use it for any other purpose other than logging in/out, demographics for our knowledge, and any voluntary feature of the site.
  * We use cookies with minimal information in them.
  * We use Google Analytics, which is covered by [Google’s Privacy policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy.html)
  * If you are below 13 then you can NOT use this site. Do NOT register if you are below the age of 13.

**In details**

  1. **What about Cookies?  
**Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser in order to check in if you are logged in or out. All the other information is located in Wrestlingfeed.com server. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our website (for example advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.
  2. **Third-party Advertisement**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).
  3. We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect _non-personally identifiable_ information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit [here](http://valueclickmedia.com/webuser_privacy.shtml).
  4. **Children below 13 DO NOT Register**  
The Federal Trade Commission’s Children Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) require that Web Sites are to obtain parental consent before collecting, using, or disclosing personal information from children under 13. If you are below 13 then you cannot use this forum. Do NOT register if you are below the age of 13.

_Note: Our Privacy Policy might Update from Time to Time, it is Your Responsibility to be updated._

  *[April 24, 2011]: 2011-04-24
